



+60-10 764 0797



zachanaz040@gmail.com



Rawang, Selangor



www.linkedin.com/in/zachroy-anazfitry

About Me

I am an enthusiastic, resilient, and lifelong learner. With over 2 years of experience, I have been exposed to and honed my skills in data analytics projects and web development. Always committed to staying up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies. I possess strong communication and am comfortable working with clients and teams.

Experience

Pipeline Network Sdn Bhd | Jun 2022 - Feb 2023

Software Developer

- Involved in full-stack development for web apps using the PHP-Laravel framework and Bootstrap 5
- Converted web design based on Figma, URS, SDS & SRS documentation by System Analysts into prototypes
- Attended meetings such as UAT with clients (government agencies) frequently to test functionality and scaling of projects
- Applied and familiar with Laravel packages to accelerate development process like Laravel Breeze, Laravel Spatie, Dompdf
- Practiced and implemented Laravel Eloquent ORM in developing and maintaining MySQL database
- Responsible and carried out APIs database integration into the web applications

Telekom Malaysia | Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

Assistant Project Manager

- Assisted the Project Manager in the management of the projects through digital transformation approach
- Designed, developed, and maintained a construction project analytics dashboard using **Power BI** features extensively
- Attended site visits and meetings for discussing projects progress

PERKESO(SOCSO) | Apr 2021 - Jun 2021

Claims Officer

- Responsible to design and build supported system for claims processing management under the Wage Subsidy Program
- Decreased claims processing time by building data integration pipeline using Talend Open Studio and Excel files
- Designed and developed KPI dashboard with Power BI and integrate it into staff monitoring system

UNITEN R&D Sdn Bhd | Nov 2018 - Apr 2020

Research Engineer

- Carried out data collection from various sources
- Cleaned, analyzed, and visualized datasets with **Python**'s numpy, pandas, seaborn and matplotlib library to extract insights
- Studied, developed, and implemented supervised machine learning algorithms for floods forecasting models using scikit-learn
- Presented research findings and progress to the Team Lead bi-weekly

Skills

Languages

- PHP
- Python

Web Design

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap 5
- Javascript

Data Science & Analytics

- scikit-learn
- Power BI

Frameworks

- Laravel
- Django
- Streamlit

Databases

- MySQL
- SQLite

Tools

- Github
- VS Code
- TablePlus
- JupyterLab

Education & Professional Certifications

2023

APU Certified Web Developer Associate (ongoing)

2022

- Python Programming by Trainocate Malaysia
- Penjana Kerjaya Python Programming for Al Engineers
- TNB Reskilling Programme Big Data Technology
- MMU Digital Ready Bootcamp Microsoft Power BI

2021

- Microsoft Certified Power Platform
- CADS Data Star Data Engineer Programme

2018

Universiti Tenaga Nasional - Bachelor of Civil Enginering (Hons.)

References

Mohamad Noramirul Bin Nordin

Senior Software Developer Pipeline Network

Phone

+6017 - 250 6256

Vanithaa A/P Ponniah

Project Management Executive Pipeline Network

Phone

+6011 - 1148 1610